sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
dareka no kitai ni zutto kotae
are you really happy
homerarerunoga suki nano desuka
when you're always meeting to someone's expectations?
naritai jibun wo surikaetemo
even if you change to who you really wanna be
egao wa itsudemo suteki desuka
will you always have a great smile?
hajimaridake yume mite okiru
dreaming of only the beginning, I wake up
sono saki nara itsuka jibun no ude de
and someday, I'll live on my own.
souda daiji na mono wa itsumo katachi no nai mono dake
yes, precious things are never in shape
te ni iretemo nakushitemo kizukanumama
you never know what it is when you get it or lose it
sousa kanashimi wo yasashisa ni jibun rashisa wo chikara ni
turn your sadness into kindness, your uniqueness into strength
mayoinagarademo ii arukidashite
even if you get lost, let's start walking
mou ikkai
one more time
Your destiny is to lose to me.
For sure.
You don't know until you try!
Your father was killed a long time ago
and I don't know the extent
of the pain you've felt...
But it's a huge mistake for you to think
that has determined your entire destiny!
You're hopeless...
Proctor... it's over.
You failure...
The Dropout's Hidden Power!
Don't... run away.
I won't... run...
I'll... stand by my own words...
That's my Ninja Way!
I'll...
stand...
by my own...
words!
That's my... Ninja Way...
I think I've heard that line before...
You with your destiny stuff...
I won't lose...
to a jerk with cold feet like you,
no matter what!
Naruto...
A brat who knows nothing
shouldn't lecture arrogantly!
People are born burdened with
an inherent destiny that they cannot defy.
Neji... live...
You're a man who is blessed
with Hyuga ability
more than anyone in the family...
I wanted you... to be born
into the head family...
You can't possibly understand
the destiny of being burdened with
a mark that cannot be wiped off for life!
Yeah...
I do understand it.
So... what of it?
This brat!
Don't be acting cool...
It's not just you who's special!
Hinata was also...
suffering the same as you!
Even though she's the head family,
not being acknowledged as such...
trying desperately to change herself...
She fought you while coughing
up blood with that in mind!
You too!
The branch family that
protects the head family...
Doing all that to Hinata
just because it's an exam.
In actuality, you were just as frantic
in attempting to go
against destiny, right?
Vitality has returned to Hinata's face!
Just what I'd expect of
the ANBU Black Ops...
She'll be okay.
Now she needs bed rest.
Your 64 Chakra Points are now shut...
How are you, who can't use Chakra
for awhile, planning to fight?
At the end of the day,
you and Hinata-sama have
the same destiny!
Shut up!
With your Byakugan, labeling people
and talking like you understand!
Then... show me whether what
you're saying is true or not.
I will! I'll defeat you no matter
what and prove that to you!
Damn it... Damn it!
That being said, I don't feel Chakra at all.
It feels like when I used up
my Chakra in the training.
You possess two kinds of Chakra...
You must extract and utilize, at any time,
the other huge Chakra that
has rested inside you from the start...
That's it. The Nine-Tailed Fox Chakra...
I'll use that...
Stinking fox...
Help me out!
This is as far as the talking goes.
Proctor... I'm going to fight with
the intent to kill him!
If you're going to stop me,
please feel free.
Jeez.
Didn't I tell you it is pointless?
This time, I really can't lose!
I'll win no matter what!
It's futile... I pressed the Chakra Points...
No matter what...
Oh, yeah! Be sure to come
watch me kick that Neji's butt!
A failure beats down
a genius with effort...
His opponent might be me...
But even if that's you, Naruto-kun,
no hard feelings.
Why do you try to go against
your destiny that much?
Because I was called...
a failure!
No, no way! Chakra is seeping out.
What's the meaning of this...?
H-He...!
What in the world...?!
W-What is he...?!
It can't be... This Chakra!
T-That's... impossible!
No way! His Chakra Points
have been pressed!
This Chakra...
It's the Nine-Tailed Fox's, no doubt...
When did he master
the Nine-Tailed Fox's Chakra...?!
Here I go!
It's twisting...
What's that?!
Is that even Chakra?!
Awesome power.
More so than during the training...
I feel it!
Rotation!
What?!
His speed's gone up!
What in the world is going on?!
You!
You're confident in close combat, right?!
You're going to become the Hokage...?
I don't... think so.
Only a very small percentage of
Shinobi are chosen to be the Hokage!
Look more at reality!
Those who become the Hokage
are born with destiny.
It's not something you become
by trying to become it.
It's determined by destiny.
People must live within
their different respective currents
that can't be gone against.
I don't know what the
Hyuga destiny of hatred is!
But if you're going to say it's futile,
you don't have to do anything!
This is bad! I must use the Rotation!
After I become the Hokage...
I'll change Hyuga!
What Chakra...
That kid showed some enormous strength...
The Hyuga kid is probably...
Hey! Which one's Naruto?!
I don't know, either!
Neji's Rotation is a technique
where the body rotates,
and dodges and
repels the opponent's Chakra!
It looks like there was
more damage done to Naruto-kun
since he plunged right into the Rotation.
There's no Genin that can beat Neji...
But Naruto-kun, you're incredible...
To think you'd force him this far...
Failure boy...
Sorry, but this is the reality...
Now this is really the en...
My body...
So he left a Shadow clone in the hole
and spotted a chance to win, huh...
Believing in victory,
thinking about what's next
and acting even when getting
knocked around, huh...
The power of believing in oneself.
That becomes the power
to change destiny...
He knows this...
And he's a natural to boot.
In those conditions,
you used the Shadow Clone Jutsu
just like that...
The Ninjutsu that you're good at, huh?
I was careless...
I've... failed the graduation
exam three times...
As luck would have it,
the Ninjutsu tests that appeared
on the graduation exam were always...
infallibly the Ninjutsu I stunk at.
Clone Jutsu was the Ninjutsu...
I stunk at.
Don't be whining about boring stuff
like destiny and what not,
and how it can't be changed!
Because unlike me...
you're not a failure.
Winner of this match is Uzumaki Naruto.
ONE JAMPU ichiban SURAMU DANKU kamasu TAISON
One! first, Tyson jumps and slam-dunks
TWO are mo kore mo dosoku de HAGU KISSU I LOVE YOU
Two! he kisses and hugs everyone randomly and says "I love you"
THREE YOGA wo kiwamemasu KAREE kirai masara san
Three! Masala masters yoga but hates curry
FOUR hetare tougyuushi SANCHESU OREI
Four! Sanchez is a lousy bullfighter, olay!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
ONE kokuen bori ni bottou bodi ma haattaya san mo
One! Bodimahattaya devotes his time for digging black ships
TWO PEKIN DAKKU waiyaa AKUSHON chari de isogu CHEN RII
Two! peking Duck, action scene, Chen Lee speeds around on his bike
THREE MY KOTEKA daiji ni migakiageru POPO san
Three! Popo loves to polish his coteka
FOUR ote wo haishaku JAPANIIZU PIIPOO
Four! japanese people, now lend me your hand!
sekaijuu hora waratteru sora miagete saa tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
sekaijuu hora kawatteku minna ganbatte so tachiagatte
all over the world, the sky's smiling, so look up and smile too
OH YEAH OH YEAH OH YEAH
Oh yeah! Oh yeah! Oh yeah!
FIGHT FIGHT FIGHT
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Yahoo! I've won! I've won!
Hey Naruto...
Don't you think I was so cool?!
Don't get so carried away!
Sakura-chan...?
Sasuke-kun hasn't arrived here yet.
What's up with that kid,
making Sakura-chan worry so much?
Next time:
"Disqualified?! Danger! Moving Ahead of Schedule! The Main Tournament with Troubles!"